hi everybody at the Staten Island
community my name is Don Linden I'm the
game director for Clara for it seems to
me that hats pound for had not an easy
start because there were a lot of maybe
a little bit disappointed fans of the
fur art nevertheless the game sold more
than 1 million copies now how do you see
this somehow paradoxical point well it's
one of those things where and what I saw
the dogs were in fact was that you know
his people some people were angry in the
beginning it still played the game a lot
I'd say you have someone complaining
like oh this game I don't like this game
you go but you played like 1200 hours of
it say it's a little bit with the
perception right because I really wanted
to take one more in a different
direction from our country in fact of
all our games that kind of be done by
different people really different as
well so I knew that some people might
not like the direction I try to balance
of thanks you know try and make
everybody happy but in the end like we
said in the panel it comes time to make
it the game that you want this wall
right I don't want to make a game that I
don't totally agree and I fought like
the whole the sort of really narrow
historical thing very micro heavy that
what he was can I'd run its course I
didn't really know how could you prove
that without say drop him the amount of
detail but people who liked at all oh
boy anyway we're doing now well we
didn't know on release was that it was
gonna be really really popular in old
history so if you notice the early stuff
wasn't that as much
oops are adding more more packs in it
that proven to be really really popular
yeah that's point my next point that's
one for seemed to me more to be sandbox
game and now also about alternative
history then I work for two simulation
instead was this deep basic game design
decision early on I won't solve to go
that direction but the the game is
designed in a way that it has to sort of
simulation and then I put things like
focus trees to restrict action system to
make it behave where it was like how
free was built around just AI
decision-making they were scripted which
is what Brooks alright this way if
something started going on this
treatment I figured this would be a much
more flexible way of doing it we still
have some ways to go when it comes to
some of the focuses interacting and we
have ways when you start going old
history and it comes from all of the
blocks hitting is almost going to be
some some cases there's something right
yeah yeah it's basically in time so I
didn't really know it's gonna pan out so
we didn't put that much effort into it
let me know we're trying Bowser effect
between historical and a circle okay
um in the upcoming patch or did you see
I don't know few who will be introduced
you told us here will be yeah as I
talked about in the panel as well
imagine maintaining two games one
without fuel how would I even ask them
possible here starts on the tank right
yeah if the tank is really good but it
requires for you and then you remove the
fuel like what it would have been very
thing for tanks and that was a point a
lot of players who wanted how will this
change the gameplay few yeah it will
generally it means that you're gonna
need to think about when you use your
use the stuff the users feel right
UK Konami just go like I'm gonna point
down my entire Navy
and will not move it and it's just gonna
all be there because you're not gonna
have the fuel to do that kind of stuff
you can't around the entire Navy even if
you're UK with a lot of resources
overseas and stuff it's not really
practical and we'll see balance wise
America so we'll talk because they've
did the pilot resourcefully will see
we're in the balance wise there for
Japan very much so you don't need to be
smart with the early you're maybe
they're gonna do but to offset because
on these nations now like Germany and
Japan I'm gonna have a little tougher
Mabley I mean they have a pretty tough
time but there are some sneaky things
you can do right to get around it we're
trying to bars that up by changing some
of the other mechanics to kind of
benefit them so I'm making raiding much
harder to stop and much more impactful
and things like that so so even running
a small Navy should be something that
you want to do rather than I feel like
the way you play now is like and their
focus on me there I don't at all you
know so it should be very good battle
back to just have science and it's the
same point with tanks for Germany yeah
so if you look at tanks and stuff the
difference it will do right because now
the way it works is that oh it gets kind
of calculated to you know your your
lifetime of fuel usage it is built into
like the the tanks that you build from
the beginning it creates a little weird
thing that you can't really build tanks
during a period you don't have fuel
where's like after you'll actually be
able to build tanks and then capture a
source of fuel and then start running
and stuff like that so it's gonna be
much more less fragile I think that kind
of stuff so you can still kind of
prepare stuff even if you're temporarily
missing and I'm you manage to get access
I think what it will mean though is that
we can make tanks stronger because we
can own limit how much you can use them
how much effectively in your armor they
are with the current system
right
effectively you could have a theory
around like a full tank army if we have
made them as comparatively good as I
kind of wanted but now there's a lot of
an actual limitation which is you need
to have a few and you won't be able to
do it like boy 3 will spotlight infinite
amounts effectively no I mean
there wasn't really a cap right so so
instead of making it very interesting in
my free what it led to was that like
people knew how much they need to just
dedicated the time to fill that out and
then it wasn't really a mission to you
anymore we hoped it was still feel like
there's an issue now and even we wanted
to feel like everything a big impact on
your performance if you really go I
don't want to have to worry about it I'm
gonna build you know good luck my
stockpile
mm-hmm so I hope you're gonna get that
balance right it's very early days so
like we haven't really played yesterday
with this yet so a lot of stuff could
change okay can you give us a quick
overview of the other main feature of
man the guns yep coming to see just a
quick yeah yeah so it's gonna be again
it's early so I can't say all that much
the focusing heavily on naval warfare
you're gonna be able to design ships you
can be signing for you know for it to be
good of different things ship
composition is gonna be a sort of fleet
compositions gonna be more important you
gotta be able to reflect fleet which
means that you all ships you can bring
them up it'll be more modern standard
this will actually cost you industry so
it's not like really repair or anything
like that
so it'll be a trade-off like do you just
want the big fleet UK probably needs a
big fleet because it needs to cover
lower area a more offensive nation
probably will do it like Germany's
quality is going to be more important
the quantity for example then we are
bringing in some focused really gonna be
focusing on the walkers is a bit from
this and it's too early to talk about
the features that will be there for
democracies but the big poster poster
boy of the expansions America and
they're going to be all test three paths
where communists income on the rice
there's going to be here a potential for
a second American Civil War against the
South wait like both sides of course you
will find out more on the future but
exactly how the story is found up to it
but but it's possible for them to get
support from abroad the trailer has
actually you know a german cruiser with
aluminum flags now imagine that the
germans would benefit from doing kind of
supporting this side right okay thanks
them for many players i know
the AI is one of the biggest issues of
heart of iron maybe the big problems for
them what are you doing on this front I
feel honestly of the way compiler that
with the huge strikes of AI that's when
I really started seeing people like I'm
not sure I can do it anymore daylights
beating in the air and starting up
oh man the guns the big focus is gonna
be on naval a I obviously to match the
other stuff because all mostly the name
of AI is really weak and it's not very
interesting opponent as some of that is
just because are credibly punishing
making mistake in the naval warfare is
you mess up one battle and then you flip
this government but the naval air needs
to be be smarter and found an
interesting opponent right
if you can be playing American jealousy
expansion the Pacific world I love
opening all that is really importantly
how you manage your pleats around that
right and for that to be found there is
to be good at it so that's gonna be a
main focus but of course we'd be looking
at you know other boxing stuff as well
one of the things that we've been kind
of wanting to focus on that is gets
brought up a lot is this concept of
suicide attacks okay I will will will
find something that it has failed to to
hold any kind of growing itself down so
that's I think it's an area is gonna
have some improvements because there are
some exploits going on there would you
be the stronger it seems to me that
you're working out of problems very
systematically battle plans air war with
men the guns the neighbor warfare yeah
what are the next big points you want to
tackle I almost like to see so the
reception isn't the expansion a little
bit before we know if you put it this
way I think politics is one thing that
could do a bit more Allah Akbar instill
doesn't have a spy system either Intel
and all of that is it's very rudimentary
it's based on taxonomy that could be
much deeper and for interesting
integrate in everything there is a
supply the supply system solves the
problem right you can get cut off and
all that stuff it kind of moved out it
simulates the stuff that basically needs
to be simulated but it's not that fun to
interact with you in fact you're very
little interaction
notice really when you're in trouble and
I think ethically succeeded compared to
four three which had a much more
detailed system but not necessarily more
control but it was very very hard on the
stand I think that at least ours is a
little better there but I would like
that system to be something that and you
yourself off the planet you know it's a
real game mechanic well that means you
know planning depots building railways I
don't know right it's in the future but
I really want to realize you're planning
your offensive also plan like how's your
logistical operation gonna be handle
this okay for me or to our own it is
again more about the planning rather
than the tactical bouts
so those are generally D'Angelo and I've
been pushing them what I must is
something like a memo for ideologies do
you think about that there are my met
modes yes I can't stop thinking about
that but it's one of those things that's
been like on the quality of life list or
a super long time but they always go in
there they're always full of it and we
don't have time to put them in but also
definitely needs something maybe the
line of force like you can see which map
nodes are gonna be like you know you
forget the most important ones being
that you care about the wine is mostly
mostly player not more than one player
yeah so I've received a happening in the
future I can't promise for this
expansion may be many more okay
is there a country that is undervalued
by the players so we have given a lot of
content but which is barely played hmm
it's a good question actually
I think some of them or because they're
situational
Czechoslovakia actually let's go with
France mr France as all the lame trees
it's done please plate all right when I
took two experienced players there was
gone at all it's one of my favorites
because it has you have a lot of
interesting choices and stuff it's quite
you know it can be quite difficult and I
think a lot of people don't try it
because they do not have this conception
or you know the other strict sense you
set up to lose historically or let's not
write mmm
it's clearly something that a lot of
people like like to play I keep hearing
it that's like when they say that the
favorite it's the favorite tree to play
on it when I look at numbers it's at
least played on all the majors okay and
what's your personal favorite theater of
all right now where do you like to play
most I kinda wanna say probably actually
Asia of the tiger I think we had a lot
of fun stuff going on there
I hope was the next one it's gonna be
the Pacific okay I am personally not a
big fan of playing America because I
don't think that I don't have the
patience to get into the world
yeah so for me I'm hoping we can give a
lot more freedom there if I'm a ball to
our trade offs but I'm hoping that the
Pacific worldly fun I've had some fun
times and what if they multiplayer and
Pacific you were on stuff like that and
I kind of really want to tighten up and
that's gonna be the future favorite one
mine okay yeah that was it thanks for
this interesting interview