all right so Holland leaning heavily on
his allies here but as allies all
picking up the slack here yes Casteel
are here they're obviously doing an
ecology mission there they're on tour
but not one step beyond Paris is what
they do in the last session we saw the
March up here take one look at burgundy
guys photo op finally deal they're on
the way
you must you must feel a skate oh no no
go a little bit farther we'll get there
eventually lads don't you worry cats
does his normal things as Goodman cats
I'm helping Lowell
bravely marching into friendly territory
sending sending artists making fake
copies of Italian art to Gujarat is very
profitable to business okay I don't
think that is actually a feature in the
game group could it be you know maybe
actual things that are happening
do we have Gujarat getting some
knowledge-sharing
from trans Oceania no so if we take a
look over it good you're at in their
home area which includes whatever cancer
did he move his capital there that is
not the gujarati capital i know in any
case it's around here and the world what
we can see is the renaissance is now
being fostered here thanks to the
knowledge sharing between them but not
for mold
no not for molten or some favoritism
here he does not care about the
Renaissance no it's not necessary
Mike SC still well despite getting all
this knowledge he's also at war and he's
fighting go back - is this his own war
or is he defending he's attacking
bomani's the Gujarati conquest of West
Berar I like this you know big nation
and he's going for it
yes very admirable yes John poor in his
side malwa but not Moulton he's not
dragging more turn into this nope
what could it mean though in fact Wow
he's actually brought in quite the
coalition on this is it his own war yeah
it is
I wonder if he wants to make his way to
the fabled mines of golconda it produces
a huge amount of diamonds so you want
that your diamonds are forever according
to Shirley Bassey well they can be yeah
good you're a plus John pure alliance
you smug gifts I know what you're saying
let's just bring back painful memories
doesn't I'm not sure if they really
happened so maybe the knife gets twisted
more with every passing day right so am
brought to this of war was someone
Bratton a you know I have high hopes for
Kazan and he's making me I mean it's
been picked at the Pope at the post
rather and the Pope was Pippin Lots but
no Byzantium reached Crimea first yeah
but was it a race to know lots of
different wars but yeah Byzantium the
Byzantine conquest of theodoro brought
them to Crimea and he's going what are
you gonna do about that Kazan well yeah
a bit clearly bratter decided to get his
place at the Black Sea there as well get
a little benefit yeah but again this is
the land that he should want this his
his religion
it's his culture group you know it's a
fairly big culture group with guitars
need some of this land to become the
great Whore if he wants to become golden
golden yes to get Crimea does have to
get I thought it was same man sir
he needs quite a lot of different land
so we can double-check that we look at
the reform in Golden Horde oh you cheeky
beggar Byzantium he took trim is the
only only one person slayed to tag
change in this game oh he's gone for it
now Kazan could fight him but he'd have
to bring in some heavy stuff cos did he
lose an ally
he dropped Ethiopia soon as Ethiopia had
served its purpose yeah he uses and
abuses does the Kaiser he didn't even
give me GOP anything I bet he promised
them land we can check that in fact so
if we look at Byzantium and look at
Ethiopia no trust there I don't think
they're happy about that yeah Brook
aligned so he promised if you
be a mom looking inland and did not
deliver how many other promises will
will the Kaiser break today how many
nations will the Kaiser break he's
growing though yes no he's using his
patented coalition away technique almost
being a war with someone wished the
coalition's away by tacking I wonder if
that's why went to war because Crimea
would have gotten a lot of aggressive
expansion there but I think that the
Kaiser was a war first so this was
Crimea jumping in to try and get his bit
unless some deal was done
hmm possibly but I don't think Oh an
uneasy border here between a hunk and
Caban hunky Caban hmm should we keep an
eye on our coalition war see well guys
there's always someone else now oh I
told you that Byzantium was going to be
the aggressor says do you know who he's
talking to
I think he's saying everyone really if
we look at was an T and I started this
was 741 development now they have 826
and a new massive vassal with 95
developments so in fact which is just
blew the limit Rennicks ation there's no
there's no development oh no I thought
was a hundred about oh it's out for
actually and there's some March stuff
relating to development but there's not
he's not a fringe in on any of that
alright so how does our coalition war
going yeah coalition II oh wow they're
pressing on Paris the castilian should
have just stayed barely the Castilians
had helped but where are they where are
the custodians it's a questionnaire oh
no they're up in Fe cellent so you're
gonna say they're up in England oh
they're just chilling out here yeah good
obviously they decided we have to we
have to defend here instead of helping
Paris yeah well they I think the god
what about the English troops why why
are they fighting says cats Oh for you
my friend the war is over
what I did not think we're talking white
piece here no no it just it's just me or
does and did he lose anything
I'm just looking at Brandt Barbara Kean
dear
does it look bigger am I just imagining
things I don't know but we can check we
can have a look at the truces that they
have and it's only a it's a little
more than five years so maybe they paid
a bit or something maybe I'm just
imagining but burgundy lips just a
little bit thicker
oh when albert van has finger dies
personal you you with England could it
be he's 33 really neat or not doing so
great
[Laughter]
people are slagging off the French
performance here the thing about these
coalition wars is it's taken away a lot
of targets that the others in this
triumphant could eat themselves and
France just isn't growing no I mean I
should be a small need lost land to
Burgundy baby oh no not your province
should be long gone
burgundy should be just calm burgundy
keeps drawing the coalition's and why
it's a hungry in water reducer oh dear
rumbling regroup well reduce has already
been pushed out of Ragusa so I do feel
for the Selassie no notice that the
Kaiser of course took the gold mines of
Kosovo for only maybe he will kindly
give it to Sun gear now I will see hmm
maybe not as much there okay Milan is
feeling the burn but this time not Savoy
in mantle
how the mighty have fallen fighter well
I mean it was I mean he got welcome to
welcome to the stream message from
Stalin and also the Pope took land
despite having tons of aggressive
expense I think it's to keeps feeding
him yeah okay so he's chilling out so
Austria is currying favor with God boss
present he was currying favor with
whatever these things can be called
Norse the old gods the cold Germans not
to mention the Hungarians or both
okay so Brandenburg they're back baby
yes Brandenburg is back groovy time to
ho join yeah
and try to get that chessboard I do
close staying right underneath any
limits of coalition
yeah well he's actually probably wanted
that for his vassal so where are the
Brandenburg cores here both of these so
he's gonna want both of those heading
over to - yes Brandenburg
coalition no sneaking a guard my
immediate northern borders I see all the
propaganda my he's saying Kazan is the
real threat everybody or is it Lithuania
or perhaps moldovia or maybe hungry
that's what he's seeing this and
note-taking Teuton we do not know why
you don't know why Poland is doing
nothing Poland just clearly playing
chess
yeah well he's about to have a border
with Byzantium and we know that doesn't
go down very well nice once you grace my
horses so Bratton thinks he's the
sneaker to start the border nice oh you
know ma'am looks into taxes Oh clear war
what do we have here Aragon and Castile
QQ what what is all this France as well
tell us more but gets tarragon Aragon is
underage he's great a like you cute why
did he a like you q2m too bad to attack
Byzantium then Byzantium say that attack
Mameluke instead yeah there was chess on
far too many dimensions I hear Lithuania
in particular is known for excellent
grazing land scarce
oh my Carsten is another person
well-versed in telling people that the
threat is somewhere else star nanowar
star now what's the up to then eaten up
the last of it
well no actually Venice appears Obie
Venice Venice is on the rise you'll
never take them alive yes Venice Rises
blue flames yes a deed that beats play
Awards yeah we were reminded every day
for several months and eventually got in
yes it was actually added it yep and
he's promised that's if he gets
eliminated from the stream he will
reboot Fitz well you're as fearless
leader now yes so I'll fight him
sometime oh but the vast ice Ragusa so
it's dead
I just wanted to check that no heat you
took but so the Kaiser allowed him a
province a single province very generous
of him yeah why not
but I think the car went since I own
Kosovo I
the rest of the lands in the area and
when is he gonna turn around and take
the rest of this area and I don't know
mmm more tributaries been a snub
hammering patch probably when we four
become competitive Oh what are you
getting out there
thank goodness be chat we have one of
our players here saying you know I used
to play competitive ice hockey but this
is the most pumped he's ever been free
no csgo I must be thinking of somebody
else but I know I was same seborrhea
yeah they were talking about different
speed csgo edu forward oh okay I was
telling me about ice hockey maybe talk
to someone else is gonna talk about his
his crotch a that he plays it was me
stop being a jet and start fighting the
Teutonic order yes invade Teutonic order
prophets you're the Allied with what the
Teutons livonian order I mean I mean
this is a perfect made war for the PLC
there one little unit gets livonians
pull and gets the Teutons it's a
beautiful thing yeah they can make the
McCall belligerent and plead for the
fancy sneak a bit of Riga in there as
well because they need to be removed
from the map with fire I go to play for
the fans I got a fan club blue boxes
need for hype somebody's suggesting that
officer is trying to prevent the shadow
kingdom he'd have a long way to go
because he'd have to rein in Savoy as
well well that's probably next in his
shopping list
quite possibly let's get the Imperial
map mode here yeah so he'd have to carve
up forensic Sienna genoa and Savoy is
not a lot of time to do it if France
would pull his finger out and actually
conquer something but he keeps getting
he keeps getting sucked into Holland's
coalition Wars and now he's sucked into
the Aragon war I think England and
Castile are playing France help a
certain this war help us out in this war
you don't have time to fight burgundy we
need to do this other wall my fans tape
s4c barrier 1s Adorno this to Jake says
he's wearing an isle of Riga t-shirt and
calls for the removal of Riga yes I do
love Riga yes site of chips we just we
just don't
mine too ones as long as we could love
it mmm all we need to know oh yeah all
he needs US equity Scotland dead well if
it's still there good place when
schooler no what would you rather the
old Perth or than you want definitely
than you more war says door this what
could it mean
oh he's at war with QQ again and has all
these miscellaneous allies come in is
the Pope in let's see are you at war
with the Pope no but you are what were
the mom looks so is he gonna go for a
second helping amounted to summer the
date this owner that aligns yet he is at
war the Pope has joined the war the Pope
is entering this battle this sure is
going to march off right now and show
Hungary who's boss or not any mobile yes
yes soon coming soon the war dear youth
okay so here we go back in muscle he
knows how this goes is four four five to
cannoneer general ripping those walls
apart with his bare hands all while the
man looks are still burned-out t he must
be going on not this again
well maybe you can actually get back
Syria he could try but I don't think
it's gonna happen the timorous have also
joined in he's lost his course on Syria
because Byzantium forced it to forced
her to give them back to Syria oh that's
how that was underhanded I was well
thought but oh my and thanks to them not
door they did get involved in the other
war so they're clearly too busy to fight
hungry it's not in this war says someone
no it's just Byzantium Syria Timur it's
this time yes oh yes oh site step aside
step this more yeah and there's a thing
that can skulls for the Holy See says
Heiser knows how to use the AI to his
advantage he's probably again promised
Timur is land probably not gonna give
him that land but it's there to just
carve up the QQ and nobody and nothing
is stopping him he's growing like the
red weed go groovy sources well
transoceanic could weigh in on this one
now is your time to strike for the
timbren so I couldn't have a better time
to strike fourth yes this is your chance
to show the term rates who's the real
term
I don't think Byzantium is gonna care
that much not enough to go and save
Timur well even then he's got a fight
his way through all the way through QQ
mm-hmm
time to have a committal East again this
is tragic but you know the Mamluks
should be calling out to people listen
Poland Lithuania
porphyria I've taken this opportunity to
get rid of some one bunch of Crusaders
yeah well they they timed this poorly
and because the Kaiser is taking brutal
advantage of depends well cuz I'm do
something try and seize Crimea mmm
I wouldn't count on it no where's his
army anyway so this is all he has to
offer
oh well he's taken the opportunity to
fight Kakashi ax and bringing in denmark
perm trans Oceana
what in the world transfer yeah now what
probably offering something for everyone
here nothing to him no why why Bri
what's going on why really it's like we
can't do it alone yes that support
managed to get into this more yet I'm
sure he's on his way
no he's he's got some clerical paperwork
for us to catch up on right yeah Oh
far as FAR's above all sure how it's
done yeah and the proof is blockading
there yeah
the poop is doing something I'm
disappointed
and if or someone says no it won't be a
pianist nobody gets Bratton's involved
in oh what Oh cuz hands what no no no
it's just concrete knowing here's the
thing though why would the Pope do
nothing if he just sits there and lets
Byzantium grow do you think Byzantium is
going to pass up the opportunity in
regards of the way
Aragorn decided no no so I haven't oqq
helped them they decided they would not
help q.q what so lots of loans coming in
for the Pope yes loan offers at least
but he's just he's not bringing the
fight
and look at this is poor fleet it's
getting B's I like when Kaiser do all
had the same trick twice and gets away
with it says the group there nobody
nobody's standing up to the Kaiser so
whenever it's active and bad memories
are 12:04 so there goes our people fleet
yes Kaiser you ants wondering with the
groups on a boat yeah somebody said 666
I didn't see somebody with a 666 but
this beating Hungarians that the siege
is farcical OTO non-aggression pact with
Austria surely yeah for three sessions
yes getting away with it although didn't
he used to have an alliance with Austria
no he never is facing both directions
here so so here's the thing everybody's
just letting the Byzantines grow
I think cousin doesn't want to let them
but he's not in the best of situations
to help out here but if the PLC cuz I
would just weigh in here Byzantium would
be no more nope but instead they're just
letting them grow it's a similar mistake
to what cats did in the last last dev
clash where he saw the trouble brewing
in India and he decided I'm gonna pick
on the weaker guy yes and that worked
out well for it well I've never seen a
nation carved up quite so bad yeah well
first he tried to form preparator yeah
character you know taking the white
piece was a mistake thought man there
was only five stop times I minus two
stabilities I think he was actually stop
it out quite likely okay so
Kaiser's back in he's got the morale
he's got the everything he's got the
reinforcements coming in oh it doesn't
seem to be winning this battle - well
Batman it's to die stroll there is yeah
but he more than makes up for it with
his generalship for for no it's nobody
there he is there's mr. for six for one
the generals just get better and better
I think that's for letting the stroll
for you and pretty incredible know who
says so Bob looks out it's got religious
ideas as well yeah semantics alright
yeah I don't know what they did they
probably took a white piece
oh if they did then that means a
five-year true all that's
worse situation than before the war Oh
misty me Byzantium is just on a roll
here and like we said nobody even trying
to stop them well except for FAR's yes
ours is bringing it ours is given their
all they gave up and present on the
capital but oh there go well the right
farce gave it at least the Pope is oh
well he's out he's faced out z-height oh
dear the skies are you add care by
aggressive expansion from our experience
no no the East Caesar is like a Medal of
Honor just my sister it's just a number
maybe thinks it's like legitimacy and
prestige you the higher it is the better
right do you know getting PSP flashbacks
from the last phosphates or so Moulton
they're just quelling the rebels Gujarat
oh good rap they did go for a Golconda
the diamond mind is theirs well I'll be
it you'll be if he if he slaps on the
merchants estate there it's gonna be
buckets and buckets for him he just has
to get the get it cord up yes beyond be
good coalition Byzantium yes he could
yes but Oh busy getting trashed by
Livonia no no he's overrun the laponia
audience there there we go they're all
they're all done with you just go hunt
down the EM yeah the stragglers whilst
pull and finally makes a move on the
Teutons oh I swear I saw something but
we'll just let blondie keep doing what
he does yes oh never mind he say never
mind never mind this I don't look don't
look
yes does this a victory card yes it does
I believe serious currently said to you
in the Byzantine victory card yeah oh I
don't think that's gonna stop them
anytime soon so where's our victory
cards looking there we go yeah there we
go it's over in Aleppo I've learned from
guru key don't look okay yes well what
is a little etiquette we get an overview
of all the victory cards so hungary has
one on poland yeah now you could have
moved in on polish territory earlier but
he decided no
than any that hung hungry hungry so will
Austria take this coastline eventually
we don't know Castilla steal on France
England on France France England Iceland
England and burgundy yeah but here's the
thing I think France are getting played
like a fiddle here
well definitely what France has done is
they've strengthened their neighbors why
their neighbors that both have victory
cards on them you know let the English
get a get a toehold in here with Flemish
land you know where where's the loyalty
going to be for Holland I wonder is it
going to be to the person on the
mainland that can snaffle them right up
or will it be with his glorious Island
benefactor who knows just just think
your Dino is getting wheeled by cars are
you're gonna get it yes I'm afraid to oh
it's it's not pretty if your Dino you're
going to destroy a player's nation when
he isn't even here that's real evil okay
so denote unable to respond on the
battlefield is these mean and I was
taken to the comment section to to lay
down the justice indeed not happenin oh
here comes a Kaiser he's going in yeah
this isn't gonna be enough to keep the
Kaiser at bay he does have the advantage
of terrain but I don't think it's gonna
give no it's flatland a flat land and
he's managed to close a good bit of the
morale but know that that general
generals taking names jeez it's man
against boys here
no what's the development now in if Stan
Constantinople pretty high for a fee not
bad 43 it's got gems as well so they
they become diamond the district whose
mallanna warith people inquiring minds
want to know everybody yes and Genoa is
finishing Amalfi
so I mean Savoy came in for know Farah
Austria took Milano or male and whatever
you want to call it and now Jenna was
gonna snuff out that light Oh needs to
rush it worries your ideas is you
weren't even trying is Kiki doesn't have
to like look at the massive army that he
has he started with a force limit of
about fifty when we started all this now
he's got sixty three with these generals
just keep rolling on in it's incredible
for siege as well can nobody stop the
Kaiser does nobody want to stop the
Kaiser and that's cuz the Kaiser want to
stop themselves
no no hey hey so hungry give fight Oh
mmm that's that's a bit cruel Dino has
asked Ashley to come in to M where after
he's going off to GDC next week but he
has said I'd like to rejoin the day of
class he's itching for it okay I wonder
if this is nothing at the edge he's
don't think D don't stink safely in the
closet maybe googy will save the burning
denote I don't know home that's a lot of
saving to do I mean perhaps these guys
are saying not my problem wait so it's
on my doorstep well it's on their
doorstep okay
what could they even do about it and
transoceanic still not working on Tim
roots here I would have thought they'd
be just trying to slaughter them instead
he's taking on too much more you know
pick on someone your own size
you you Keck who's Kang yeah those guys
whatever they're called so
and then there's Kazan what are the
Castilians doing in Kazan the expert did
I have volunteers tourists somebody
please tell me
theorem they removed the alliance with
somebody and I didn't notice that's why
you may have won the battle but you
don't well you won't win the war or the
trophy oh is that a curse he is only in
second you aren't converting to a body
well actually no I think Alexey value
sadly cannot make this session he's
actually away on holiday next week so
you didn't take part he decided to
emulate the Kaiser and single players he
started as the Ottomans flipped through
one country went to the Byzantines and
then he went Coptic and he said that was
all P putting the o P into all P into
Coptic yes
okay so Byzantium is number one in score
from all the players Mamluks in second I
don't think they're gonna stay in second
for very long and then the usual
suspects yes yes I'm on the board for
innovativeness says Groody how is he
how's he doing with there he's managed
to get some innovation there and a new
innovation from the group I saw Kazan
allied with Castile and France plus PLC
and Denmark I want to take a quick look
to see how people are doing it
innovativeness first where's the
technology I don't know there we go
so who's who's captain okay so Byzantium
unsurprisingly leading the way in
innovation in Holland
yeah hold on do not too bad Erica yeah
it's kind of a kind of a long game but
you really reap the rewards there your
own we'll fight to the last Legionnaire
Oh Rome didn't fight a single
Legionnaire so I think he's talking
about him it's a third C Alliance for me
how's it cool it should formed against
them know nothing of the sort
Blair what is what is the no no you stop
those guys are you insane Roman fight -
lastly there's only one room I know and
yeah by GM check cosines Alliance stats
because that's what people click dead
could it be transoxiana as well that is
quite an alliance
Casteel France Poland Lithuania Denmark
not Sweden oh we got the pole up here to
see who will win we'll check her votes
here oh no we can make it more we can
vote all right can you only vote once
yeah fraid so
oh man I want to believe in the God
himself
okay well vote for the Pope yeah I think
it was up near the top yes there you go
okay I believe in the Pope
let's see who's winning Oh Starlin is it
what are we already voted Oh what sorry
ah somebody in this office is playing
with us Kaiser Johannes currently
favorite followed by star followed by
farce apparently people believe in the
eyes speaking of children he's in a
player war he is killing another player
on the belt and Milan is down and out so
cuz then is this a case of don't look
don't look
cuz that's a lot of friends yeah there's
enough friends can to get QQ say oh can
I get QQ say no more my home bait BAM
Luke's well QQ is enjoying a truce so
they won't be able to ma'am looks their
truths doesn't last long if they destroy
Byzantium Mamluks can come in yeah her
own accord maybe that's why they were
all right Kaiser he's got a lot of
manpower he's got money
he's got sailors stability little
corruption max prestige louver extension
he's got he's camping every number he
can find he's going for it but can he
stand up to this will his friend Hungary
help him out what of Sweden
what of Timmy Ethiopia the other
background he's making friends again old
friends come come help me but there is a
lot of disease he's eating attrition
there he knows what's coming but he has
a forty Rory it's a swamp it's a dutch
fort dutch fort they are brimming with
dutch fort show the alliance map mode of
kazan ooh
england notably sing my problem
well basically mu
handed mammoth some detailed
instructions and apparently mammoth
switches over to war and peace when he
wants a bit late reading cool issued war
against Byzantium was covered or not he
may be currently picking his master to
find out haleh the star nine Kaiser says
people are asking what the Vell fair
master is doing well Portugal's just
chillin but he's he made it to the New
World
oh there we go he's taken the good
places he's going to the Caribbean he's
off to Havana he wants he's got the West
Indies he's Loki and Titan there must be
a Portuguese West Indies appeals soon
one can only hope but he doesn't
currently have any not so man I saw him
in a war earlier houses Marley's over in
the Mallee right oh yeah and he's eating
up more he's sticking at the bond of man
and the Oh yo and rightfully so because
this land is because he's got a long
fight for revenge
he's got was gold here but it's Looby
he's been he's going off to fight his
way up and get this is not the nicest of
places to be but at least you're pretty
free from the players slaughtering you
especially when you have Zeke or the
letter Z over in Portugal he's not the
hi-- aggressive no he said Peter no high
octane he wants more to Val fair I
wonder if this is just a trick to make
Byzantium just calm down
well certainly it's definitely meat I
mean the character is not you know Peter
Warne I for at least five minutes with
your fighters dead Fido is gone Fido of
us left the building
any people voted for Fido - oh well good
both of those people stand up and pay
your respect yes optimism there we
employ a couple of fans that are nuts oh
man there I noticed so Molly Molly can
bring it all back they say I think one
that maybe themselves mom Oh Mamie oh
there's a lot of fans coming out of the
woodwork you pay the respects for fight
over there pay the ferryman
okay so quite a few but Denmark leaving
themselves a robo fight total war that's
a no pre she got off of competition
games please what are you saying is he
could play two games at one yes he
probably is he's faced at two he's such
a bastard
are people waiting what will Hungary do
I worry a bit for Denmark if Sweden are
gonna play well in their alliance here
Denmark is left wide open
yeah but then again oh yes don't grow
did separatists those people aren't
we're not brothers em coming soon
yeah ii soon - enough god near you Kazan
maybe there
maybe Kazan are on the case there but
Novgorod is woodland so they wouldn't
get their awesome horde bonuses for it
what's the Dutch aggress it's benched
like well well I mean it's been a while
since we did a coalition war yeah and
he's finally chilled out enough so he
probably won't get punitive strugglin
again touchwood okay so the khazzani
looks like we're gonna take care of
locked door first and then move into
novgorod well as well start with small
rebels yeah
the danes are running back again you
can't do this if you want that coalition
you got to fight as a unified force mmm
well the guys are strike willing to go
for a peaceful here head to the war his
claims on the Kazan yes
oh no the Kazan one terrible woman will
they take trim if they do reach that
level and this point no Franz could seal
there
we're burning for no good reason here
nope
my thing is a Byzantium kinda wants to
be attacked so it's good friends
Ethiopian Timur it's will help them out
but then again Tim roots are enjoying
rebel sandwich here might not work out
for them people involved here any work
old oh it's that time be on be going and
to finish off Crimea yes he is from sea
to shining sea nah not interested in
this and this bigger war he knows his I
said elsewhere alright can Byzantium be
contained the star 9 he is a war with
someone having finished off Fido he's
not gonna stop there he wasn't sure Noah
as well well I wonder he's given the
Pope a bit more land yeah I wonder if
he's taking it in just giving it to the
Pope I was approved getting so much line
we did see him call the Pope into a war
and then give him land in a piece
radar/laser is a board for Tennessee's
migrating a bit
he saw well there's nothing left at
today's well miss Abu had a good runner
this the hot damn yeah I guess they're
being growing artificially by Morocco
but more power to mazhab so what if this
there's a still me now I'm gonna really
save ice do not start a war that you
don't finish that session because a war
that goes on for two sessions your enemy
gets a perfect opportunity to plot Dino
to war what could it mean he hasn't
discovered South America yet but he's
off to take on these guys this happens
to be our new country so they've beep
ass we need to stop we need to remove
countries frankly it's a new direction
to take the game but yes supported stone
and should backstop the Western alliance
people are saying they'd be in a perfect
position to do so leaving their lands
wide open look at this anybody
I bet nuts a man wishes he was still in
Burgundy at this point maybe he's gonna
try and fight his way through haha well
I don't think we'll see any bunker back
steps here but there's the potential for
it still though they're keeping us on
tender hooks are they gonna start the
war is this just a huge bluff we've seen
it before haven't we I swear we've seen
situations where it was Daniel the salt
man where he gives everything up and in
fights at OPM HRE matt please so much
curious well I'm playing burgundy as
well he's hiss you waiting for it says
not says the Kaiser that's that's eh
sorry
oh well no you'll have it rained in
because he's got the Pope and Venice all
done so yeah that just makes it more
expensive to take but what's he gonna do
alright yeah like I say keep not some
tender hooks here well I saw the cars
are basically Golding them in chin if I
were a cunning man who had to cut this
up for YouTube later I'd be trimming it
just before war starts but yeah this
rate here you know I mean will be a
20-second clip at the end yeah come now
Byzantium I noticed that they're spying
on both man looks and Carrick you know
for what reason I couldn't possibly say
well definitely he's managed to stop
them but this threat of a war has
actually managed to stop the Kaiser
there's another threat here the Kaiser
slowed him down at least a little bit
because it's been usually the carrier's
answer to collisions is attack but I
don't think it's enough the grass
expansion with any informal call this
year because usually goes on the
offensive mean what's him
what's castile tech act cuz he's sitting
on the front line there he's so as it
conceded Castilian army tech eight
oh but Austria also have that okay tech
aids pretty good one for him to have
yeah I paid well in advance for that
it means the infantry are so much better
especially the cavalry but still war not
happening what could it mean what are
they waiting for Buren a bad move never
waits on Buren he'll be there when he
least expects it nobody expects and the
feeling an inquisition
yes but everybody's poised and ready and
doing nothing ya know mostly the guys is
working from home today to to train
problems so you will not be able to get
his take a chat debt the danes are going
home yes has the coalition fallen apart
before it's even done anything waiting
on the man looks maybe maybe hmm oh well
if that's the case that's August yeah
but he's not more with Tunisia now that
that war surely over by nobody team war
score so I don't know where the rest of
June is he is hmm yeah okay protected by
the Tennessee and fleet ah but no the
man looks are there they managed to
sneak their way over okay but the man
looks have an army once it's mostly gone
now they're ready for Ethiopia yeah oh
it is so I think that's it they want the
man looks in as well mom looks could
have also just denied Ethiopia access
but Oh Oh bad times from ham look sir
failing to be a great power anymore and
nobody I think is knowledge sharing with
them well its present but it doesn't
spread enough for him to afford it
tragic tank time is running out the site
already says declare already's call them
to declare it oh he's saying bring it he
sitting like Morpheus going bring it
well all the time he's overspending on
his army here
still in debt don't have enough money to
repay our loans oh he's only got a
couple of them though mm-hmm he's not
maintaining his army he's confident he's
he's cocky levels are confident well
that's that's Kaiser Johann mm-hmm
does bids not have allies this has
allies they are Sweden hungry
I wonder if Sweden's gonna get involved
in all this what does Sweden stand to
gain by fighting the Danes well it's
more business before pleasure yeah I see
a little smile there for body the booth
yeah okay well Olga's just come and gone
the Mamluks no longer have a truce who
the allied with that I don't know what
you're doing anymore you just you just
know what you saying don't look don't
look don't look okay okay border
conflict Kaiser smug mountains your
hands
Oh Oh guys I might have done the three
mountains but you'll never be the first
to do it
almost more Kaiser please drill all
these on the border that's one way to
say bring it yes
Oh Kaiser Kaiser has vision he's put his
boats here so he can see what's going on
yes it's like they've withdrawn their
but that's a French fleet sitting in
coop and how powerful is that
Kaiser she want to see this Kaiser of
the galleys and this is an inland sea
but France and Casteel together have
heavies which are pretty good I still
think the Kaiser has this though yes mmm
they would need somebody else with a
decent fleet somebody if only there was
a nation that you know really show their
might who happened to say have any sort
of connection with France and castile
hmm not gonna happen
all right so we're still sitting there
watching this yeah II know meanwhile I
was back on the expansion train there
yeah yeah he's got to do something well
he's doing something he's fighting to
murids of all people and I don't I don't
know why the grood isn't getting on that
certainly doesn't appear ready to be
part of this unless unless he thinks
he's gonna fight timorousness well yeah
motomete our ally is it too much to ask
for you to start a war
well this is where we need special
observer powers we can just a war yeah
that's not so - keep it on the expansion
I'm not so man can bring us some enjoy
yes that's a man they are proving Wow
yes okay this is the next rata G to put
the Kaiser to sleep yes and then fight
him but yes malli is on the attack he
even has so he vas alized what was left
to Banamine war war has finally happened
well yeah well that was maybe quite a
clever strategy who declared it okay cuz
an dead fight oh and I just heard
somebody decline the call to arms Sweden
did not join the war
Sweden's neutral more news a sad story
as at all but the Kaiser he's on the
advantage he's pressing it and he is
sending the enemy packing over Francis
coming in here there we go but is that
enough I don't think it is oh no he's
foot out to the wire France has been
told where to go oh my goodness had
people back you go don't don't flash
your arm like that it's off camera we're
[Laughter]
all right so let's check out
participants here dere tast away so
Byzantium Hungary Ethiopia Syria
yeah they got about a hundred thousand
on their site cousin Castile dead mark
fighting more than double their number
land transoxiana param nor are we
Moldavia oh the cracking perm is still
on the map life and there we are all
Poland is wicked us for constant oh wow
he knows what he wants and he's going
for it
yes he's decided the way to become the
fans favourite it's become the Byzantine
Empire yeah but that that for six for
one general is on its way Poland and
better know what he's doing better have
some backup all Hungary's got his eyes
set on it where's Lithuania is he coming
in to support show superiority oh that
was your first mistake
barbarians yes the Kaiser never sort of
confidence
how much superiority can the Pope come
on polls you need to channel your energy
he's called the tactics advantage and
morale but he just does another lumber
or numbers or the cannon getting flanked
on both sides cannons roaring yes I is
not superiority Wow ten more scored
already yikes the Kaiser is putting more
than double his number in its place
oh there our laser is in our laser is in
he's probably gonna have to get me Theo
Pio toys ignoring Ethiopia he's going
for Syria yeah he is he knows what he
wants and he wants it back
[Music]